Guida West Papers, 1946-2006
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. CONFERENCES AND MEETINGS
  - "Matriarchal Moments? New Perspectives on Women's Rebellions," Institute for Advance Study, 22 Apr 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Survival Summit, "Up and Out of Poverty Now," [various locations?] 20-23 Jul 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Second National Survival Summit, 20-23 Aug 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "Wisdom From the Past, Visions For the Future," Institute for Policy Studies 30th Anniversary Conference and Letelier-Moffitt Human Rights Awards Dinner, 2-3 Oct 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Meeting for Real Welfare Reform, 18 Jul 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "Expanding the Women's Activist Agenda: Uniting Activists, Researchers, Funders and Policymakers," 16-17 Oct 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - New York State Welfare Breakfast, 14 Nov 1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Responding to Welfare Reform," Syracuse, NY, 26 Feb 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Women Fighting Poverty" Conference V, "Winning Our Fair Share," New School for Social Research, New York, NY, 4 Apr 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "Welfare Reform and the College Option National Conference," 24-25 Sep 1999 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - "Re-Imagining the Welfare State," CUNY, 1 Mar 2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971-2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- SERIES V. INDIVIDUALS
  - [see also Interview notes in SERIES VIII. WRITINGS and audio recordings of interviews in SERIES X. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS AND COMPUTER MEDIA] (Box 5)
  - Nanette Adams, Newark, New Jersey [no interview], 1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Madeline Adamson (Box 5)
  - [see also Bert DeLeeuw] (Box 5)
    - General, 1983-86 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence and transcript, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Muriel Ayers, Montclair, New Jersey: transcript, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Judy Baldwin, FWRO of Morris County, New Jersey: transcript, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Elayne Brodie, Rochester, New York [no interview], 1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Louise Brookins, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania [no transcript], 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Barbara Brown, Camden, New Jersey (Box 5)
    - General, 1983-87 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence and transcript, 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Gail Ann Bruen, Family Services, Bloomfield, New Jersey: transcript 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Hobart Burch, UCC Welfare Priority Team: notes and transcript, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Joyce Burson, WRO: correspondence and transcript, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bertha Cavanaugh, Rhode Island [no transcript], 1973-84 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Richard Cloward (Box 6)
  - [see also Frances Fox Piven] (Box 6)
    - General, 2000-02 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Notes on conversation, 197(2)? (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bob Curvin, Bureau of Community Services, Newark, New Jersey: notes on interview, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Catherine Dandridge, Chicago, Illinois, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Maud Davis, Newark, New Jersey (Box 6)
    - General, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Transcript, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Shirley Davis and Doris McCrae, North Jersey Community Union, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bert DeLeeuw, 1984-87 (Box 6)
  - [see also Madeline Adamson] (Box 6)
    - General, 1984-90 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Notes, correspondence, and transcript, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and transcript, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Gary Delgado, Center for Third World Organizing, Oakland, California [no transcript], 1983-98 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Ruby Duncan, Las Vegas, Nevada: general, 1983-89 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - Zella Emerson, Vermont [no interview], 1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Faith Evans, UCBHM (Box 6)
    - General, 1976-96 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Notes and transcript, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Jim Evans, 1984-88 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Virginia Evans, Washington, DC, 1983-84 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Theresa Funicello, WRO (Box 7)
  - [see also Downtown Welfare Advocate Center and Social Agenda] (Box 7)
    - General, 1976-2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Transcript, correspondence, and notes, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Carol Glassman, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Tom Glynn, Boston, Massachusetts: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Ruby Grace, Essex County Chapter National Clients Council, New Jersey WRO (Box 7)
    - General, 1972-98, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Juliet Grant, Newark, New Jersey: general and transcript, 1969-71 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Roberta Grant, Boston, Massachusetts: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - David Greene, WR Support Committee: General, 1989-90 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Harriet Joyce Greenwood, Seattle, Washington: correspondence 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - [see Wofford for transcript] (Box 7)
  - Mamie Hall, Brooklyn, New York: correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Catherine Hamer, Montclair WRO, New Jersey (Box 7)
    - General, 1982-87, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Transcript, correspondence, and interview guide, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Rose Harris, Newark, New Jersey: notes, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Glenn Hatfield, New Jersey FWRO, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Margaret Hayes, WRO: partial transcript and correspondence, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Florence Henderson, Morristown, New Jersey: correspondence, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Marcia Henry, Oakland, California: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Etta Horn, Citywide Welfare Alliance, DC: notes on interview and clipping, 1970, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Kay Hurley, Massachusetts: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Espinola Jackson, California: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Claradine James, Roxbury, Massachusetts: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Hulbert James, HumanSERVE Fund (Box 7)
    - General, 1985-97, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Transcript and notes, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Kim Jefferson, Newark FWRO, New Jersey: transcript 1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Catherine Jermany, San Francisco, California (Box 8)
    - General, 1971-85 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Frankie Jeter, WRO of Allegheny County, Pennsylvania (Box 8)
    - General, 1977-84 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Dee Johnson, California: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Jean Jones, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Roxanne Jones, Philadelphia Citizens in Action (Box 8)
    - General, 1984-96 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Notes on interview and correspondence, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Marion Kidd, Newark WRO, New Jersey (Box 8)
    - General, 1970, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Notes, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Gwyn Kirk: general, 1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Marian Kramer, Michigan WRO, NWRU, Michigan Network to Abolish Workfare (Box 8)
    - General, 1988-93 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Transcript and notes, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Andrea Kydd, Michigan WRO, National Network to Abolish Workfare (Box 8)
    - General, 1986, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Robert Langer, Health and Welfare Council of Metropolitan St. Louis, Missouri, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Rosie Lee, Chicago WRO, Illinois: correspondence 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - [see also Dandridge] (Box 9)
  - Rhoda Linton (Box 9)
    - General, 1984-85 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Transcript and notes, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pauline London, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: transcript and notes, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - David Ludlow, New Jersey FWRO: notes and partial transcript, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ginger Mack, Chicago, Illinois: correspondence, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Rudell Martin: correspondence, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Ethel Mae Matthews, Atlanta, Georgia Poverty Rights Office: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - John Mayer, National Farmworkers Ministry: notes on telephone conversation, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Doris McCrae (Box 9)
  - [see Shirley Davis] (Box 9)
  - Bobbie McMahan, Southwest Community House, DC (Box 9)
    - General, 1969-80, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Shirley McNeill, Baltimore, Maryland (Box 9)
    - General, 1970, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sarah McPherson, DC: correspondence and interview guide, 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Joe Merchant, UCC Welfare Priority Team: notes and transcript, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Yvonne Perry Myles, Virginia: transcript, correspondence, and interview guide, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Hal Nelson (Box 9)
  - [see Saulsberry] (Box 9)
  - Tony O'Flaherty, Essex County Welfare Department, New Jersey: transcript, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Moiece Palladino, San Rafael, California: transcript, correspondence, and notes, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Bill Pastereich, ACORN, MassWRO, Boston (Box 9)
    - General, 1983-88 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - James Pawley, Newark Urban League, New Jersey: notes, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Shirley Smith Peoples, Columbus, Ohio: correspondence, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Brenda Perry, Newark WRO, New Jersey: notes on telephone conversation, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth Perry, DC: transcript, correspondence, and interview guide, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Jackie Pierce, Camden, New Jersey: transcript and interview guide, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Frances Fox Piven (Box 10)
  - [see also Richard Cloward] (Box 10)
    - General, 1966-91 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Interview notes, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Rafe Pomerance: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Jackie Pope, WRO (Box 10)
    - General, 1983-87 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Wade Rathke, ACORN, New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 10)
    - General, 1979-82, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Margaret Rose, Montclair WRO, New Jersey (Box 10)
    - General, 1979-87 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Transcript, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Transcript and interview guide, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Audrey Rowe, DC (Box 10)
    - General, 1987-94 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Timothy Sampson, WRISC, Citizens Action League, Oakland, California (Box 10)
    - General, 1972-2001 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Questions for interview and correspondence, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Beulah Sanders, Citywide WRO, New York City, NWRO (Box 10)
    - General, 1970-84 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Transcript and notes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Bernardine Saulsberry, Operational Emergency Center, Seattle, Washington (Box 11)
    - General, 1982, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1983-84 [with Hal Nelson] (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Coretha Saxon, National Clients Council, Camden, New Jersey: transcript, correspondence, and interview guide, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Pat Scott, Oregon, California: correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Juanita Serrano, Greater Cleveland WRO, Ohio: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Paul Sherry, United Church of Christ (Box 11)
    - General, 1971-72 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Notes and transcript, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Colleen Buckley Shillington, Ohio (Box 11)
    - General, 1986-99, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Interview notes and correspondence, circa 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Annie Smart, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, National Anti-Hunger Coalition, Annie Smart Leadership Development Institute (Box 11)
    - General, 1987, 1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Transcript, correspondence, and notes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lee Staples: notes, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Dottie Stevens, Survivors Inc., Mass. WR Union, ARMS, Boston, Massachusetts (Box 11)
    - General, 1984-2001 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Transcript, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Maureen Taylor, Michigan WRO: general 2001 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Bruce Thomas, San Francisco California (Bernard Eugene "Bruce") (Box 11)
    - General, 1982-85 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Johnnie Tillmon, ANC Mothers Anonymous, Los Angeles, California, NWRO (Box 11)
    - General, 1983-96 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Notes and transcript, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Transcript, 1983, and correspondence 1984 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Elizabeth Turner, Iowa, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Mel Turner, Maryland: transcript and correspondence, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Lucius Walker, Jr., HOME: notes and general, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Jeannette Washington, New Alliance Party, New York City (Box 12)
    - General, 1983-84, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Transcript, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Mabel Watley, Greater Cleveland WRO, Ohio: general, transcript, and correspondence, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Helen Webber, WPT: notes and transcript, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. Bruce Wells, Newark Housing Authority, New Jersey: notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - George Wiley, NWRO (Box 12)
    - General, 1969-83 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Notes on Paul Sherry interview, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Gwenda Williams, Montclair WRO, New Jersey: notes, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Joanne Williams: general, 1984, 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Marjorie Williams, Newark WRO, New Jersey: notes, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Mary Louise Williams, Seattle, Washington: general, 1982-88 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - [see Wofford] (Box 12)
  - Margaret Willis, Ohio WRO (Box 12)
  - [see also Johnnie Tillmon] (Box 12)
    - General, 1984-89 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Transcript, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Nezzie Willis, Chicago, Illinois: transcript, correspondence, interview guide, and notes, 1983-84 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Leola Wofford, Seattle, Washington: correspondence, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Leslie Wolfe: general, 1978, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- SERIES VI. ORGANIZATION FILES
  - Advocacy Resources for Modern Survival (ARMS)[Dottie Stevens], Boston, Massachusetts, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Alliance for Displaced Homemakers (national), 1977-78 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - American Civil Liberties Union of New Jersey, 1969, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - American Jewish Committee, 1969, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - ANC [Aid to Needy Children] Mothers Anonymous [Johnnie Tillmon], Los Angeles, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Annie Smart Leadership Development Institute, 1993, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Applied Research Center, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Arkansas Welfare Rights Organization, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN)[Wade Rathke], 1980-88, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Bergen County (NJ) Mobilization Against Hunger Committee, circa 1969 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Black Women United For Action, Inc., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Black Women's Agenda, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Boston Industrial Mission, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for Adequate Welfare Reform Now, 1971-72 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Center for Community Change (CCC), 1973-76 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Center for Law and Social Policy (CLASP), 2000-02 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Center for Third World Organizing[Gary Delgado], 1983, 1991, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities, 1995, 2000-02 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Center on Social Welfare Policy and Law/Welfare Law Center/National Center for Law and Economic Justice (Box 13)
    - 1972-Jul 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7-15)
    - Aug 1979-2006, undated (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
  - Central Presbyterian Church, Montclair, New Jersey (Box 14)
    - General, 1967-71, undated (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
    - Task Force on the Urban Crisis, 1967-68 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Central United Presbyterian Church, Newark, New Jersey, 1968-69 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Friends of Welfare Rights Organizations, 1970-71, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Welfare Rights Organization [Rosie Lee], 1984-85 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Children's March for Survival, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Citizens Action League (CAL), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Citywide Coordinating Committee of Welfare Groups, New York City, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Clark County Welfare Rights Organization, Nevada, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Coalition for Basic Human Needs (CBHN), 1980, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Coalition For Human Needs and Budget Priorities, 1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Coalition of Grassroots Women (NYC), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Coalition on Human Needs, 1994-2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Coalition on National Priorities and Military Spending, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Collingswood Welfare Rights Organization (Camden, NJ), 1970-73, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Religion in Appalachia (CORA), undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Committee of Concern (Newark, New Jersey), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Common Cause, 1971-75, undated (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
  - Community Action Committee, Waterbury, CT, circa 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Community Crisis Intervention Project, Crisis and Change newsletter, 1972, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Community Food Resource Center, 1997-99, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Community Voices Heard, 2005, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Consumers Buyers Club [Marion Kidd], Newark, NJ, 1971-72 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Council of Presidents (COP) Task Force on Economic Security, 1995-97, [see also National Council of Women's Organizations] (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Crusade Against Hunger (Box 15)
  - [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 15)
  - Detroit/Wayne County Homeless Action Network, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Displaced Homemakers Network, Inc., 1978-82, undated (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
  - Downtown Welfare Advocate Center (DWAC) [Theresa Funicello], New York City, 1975-79, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - [see also Social Agenda below] (Box 15)
  - Education Center for Community Organizing, 1989-95, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Empire State Economic Security Campaign (ES2), 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Essex County (NJ) Legal Services Corporation, 1969-70 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Essex County (NJ) Welfare Board, 1968-75 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Essex-Newark Legal Services, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies (Box 15)
  - [see Professional Activities] (Box 15)
  - First Presbyterian Church, Metuchen, New Jersey (Box 15)
    - Covenant of Open Occupancy, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Church and Society Committee (Box 15)
      - General (Box 15)
        - 1961-65 (Box 15, Folder 25-26)
        - 1966, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Notebooks, 1964-66 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Food Research and Action Center (FRAC), 1971-76, 1978-79, undated (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Friends of Welfare Rights of Essex County (NJ), 1968-72, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Georgia Department of Family and Children's Services, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Greater Cleveland Welfare Rights Organization (Ohio), 1970-84, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Greater Newark Council of Churches, 1965-68, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Greater Newark Urban Coalition, 1968-72, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Houston Legal Foundation, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Houston Metropolitan Ministries, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Houston Welfare Rights Organization (Texas), 1977, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Human Service Employees Registration, Voting and Education Campaign (HumanSERVE) (Box 16)
    - General, 1983-85 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Agency-Based Voter Registration Kit, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hunger Action Network, 1999-2004, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - IMPACT Interreligious Network (national and New Jersey), 1975-78, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Indian Welfare Rights Organizations, 1970-73 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Social Justice, 1979-83 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Social Relations, Catholic Archdiocese of Newark, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research (Box 17)
    - General, 1995-2006, undated (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
    - Conference "Women and Welfare Reform: Women's Poverty, Women's Opportunities, and Women's Welfare," 23 Oct 1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Welfare Reform Research Coordinating Meeting, 11-12 Jul 1997 (Box 17)
      - Briefing book (Box 17, Folder 7-10)
      - Notes (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Welfare Reform Research Coordinating Meeting, 8-9 Nov 1997 (Box 17)
      - General (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Briefing book (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
      - Briefing book (cont'd) (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
      - Speaker and participant packet (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Inter-Faith Task Force for Public Assistance Reform in Ohio, 1970-72, undated (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization (IFCO), 1969-75, undated (Box 18, Folder 6-8)
  - Jobs for the Future (Box 18)
  - [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 18)
  - Joint Center for Poverty Research (JCPR), 2000-02 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Joint Strategy and Action Committee (JSAC), 1968-80, undated (Box 18, Folder 10-12)
  - Justice, Economic Development and Independence for Women (JEDI Women), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Kansas City Welfare Rights Organization, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Kensington Welfare Rights Union (KWRU), 1992-2003 (Box 18, Folder 15-18)
  - League of Women Voters of New Jersey, 1970-73 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - League of Women Voters of the United States, 1968-83, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - League of Women Voters, miscellaneous state and local groups, 1964-71 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1998-2003, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Legal Momentum, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Legal Services of New Jersey, 1978-83 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Maryland Welfare Rights Organization, 1969-72 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Welfare Rights Organization, 1974-75, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Welfare Rights Union, 1994-96 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Memorial West United Presbyterian Church, Newark, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Metropolitan Associates of Philadelphia, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Metropolitan Detroit Welfare Reform Coalition, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Ecumenical Ministry (MEM), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan-Urban Service Training (MUST), 1965-67, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Metuchen-Edison Community Service Committee for the Kilmer Job Corps Center, 1965-66, undated (Box 19, Folder 16-18)
  - Metuchen-Edison Racial Relations Council, 1962-66, undated (Box 19, Folder 19-20)
  - Miami Valley (Ohio) Unemployed Council, 1995-96 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Michigan Network to Abolish Workfare, 1984, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Michigan Welfare Rights Organization [Marian Kramer], 1988-2001, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Middlesex County College, Displaced Homemakers Center (New Jersey), 1980-82, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Ministry of Metropolitan Mission, St. Louis, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Minnesota Alliance for Progressive Action, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Mobilization For Enough to Live On, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Monmouth County Welfare Board (New Jersey), 1971, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)